ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A Good Union Never Rests (Box 70, Folder 18)
  2nd edition; The Story of Our union: A Booklet Published for Local 105s New Members
- A Good Union Never Rests, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- A Good Union Never Rests (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Progress…Our Common Purpose, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  A report on local 105s accomplishments during its first 20 years; 1941-1961
- Know Your Union (Box 70, Folder 18)
  Questions and Answers; 7th edition
- Know Your Union, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  Questions and Answers; 8th edition
- Get More Out of Your Union Membership (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Local Ten Cutters' Almanac, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  September 1962; 1902-1962; 60th Anniversary
- Local Ten Cutters' Almanac, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  September 1962; 60th Anniversary
- Bulletin For Organizers and Active Members on the New Wage-Hour Law, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  February 1950
- Must We Have a Depression? What Can we do About it?, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Part II Summary; A Report on a Panel Discussion at the ILGWU Studio; January 18, 1947
- Trends and Prospects: Women's Garment industry 1953-1956 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Report presented by General Executive Board to the ILGWU Atlantic City Convention; May, 1956
- Trends and Prospects: Women's Garment Industry 1947-1950 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Report presented by General Executive Board to the ILGWU Atlantic City Convention; May, 1950
- The Women's Garment Industry: An Economic Analysis, 1937 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Constitution: International ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 70, Folder 19)
  As adopted by the Fortieth Convention at Hollywood, Florida, June 1989
- Resolutions Submitted to the 42nd Convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Volume III; June 1995
- Campaign for Justice, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- The ILGWU Song Book, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Illustrations by Suan A.M. Solotoff
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1939 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Souvenir Book; Boston and District Educational Council; Saturday evening, October 28, 1939
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1939 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Equal Opportunity Union Made (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Price 25 cents
- ILGWU Worker Family Education Program (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Delegate's Guide: 41st Convention, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  Fontainebleau Hotel; Miami Beach, FL; June 12-19, 1992
- The Law Says You Have a Right to Join a Union (Box 70, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Video Catalogue (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Unite and Fight: 41st Convention Policy Statements of the ILGWU, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  June 1992
- ILGWU Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  June, 1992
- Union Health Center: Celebrating 75 Years of Service, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  1914-1989
- Unite and Fight: Report of Proceedings of the 41st Convention of the ILGWU, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Unite and Fight, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Day Six; June 19, 1992
- Campaign for Justice, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Substance Abuse Manual, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Substance Abuse Manual, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- New York Post, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Monday, February 11, 1991
- Unite and Fight, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Day 1; June 12, 1992
- Unite and Fight, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Day Three; June 16, 1992
- Unite and Fight, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Day Four; June 17, 1992
- Unite and Fight, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  Day Five; June 18, 1992
- How We Tell Our Story, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Northeast Department ILGWU Health & Welfare Fund, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  September, 1985
- Cloak & Dress Drivers' & Helpers Union, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Cloak & Dress Drivers' & Helpers Union, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  Health and Welfare Benefits
- Preparing a Career in Labor Leadership (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Resolutions Introduced by Delegates to the 24th Convention ILGWU, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  May 27-June 8, 1940; Carnegie Hall, New York City
- Agreement of Merchants' Ladies' Garment Association, Inc. with International Ladies' Garment Workers Union and Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  1937-1940
- The Common Thread, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Locals 109, 365, 131; October 1984; Vol. 11, No. 2
- The Common Thread, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Locals 109, 365, 131; October, 1984; Vol. 11, No. 2
- A Brief history of the International ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Handbook: Your Union…How it Works, Your Benefits, Your Responsibilities (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Constitution and By-Laws of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 71, Folder 1)
- We Are the ILGWU (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Photos: Robert Gumpert; Cara Lise Metz; Design: Cyd Weldon
- See America in Style: A Travel and Fashion Guide (Box 71, Folder 1)
- You May Be Eligible to get Money from the Government (Box 71, Folder 1)
- UNITE Fight (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Bumper sticker
- UNITE Fight (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Bumper sticker. Copy 2.
- UNITE fight (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Bumper sticker. Copy 3
- This is Worth Fighting For: Annual Report for 1942 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No. 32 and the Administrator: Vol. 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Differences in Living Costs in Northern and Southern Cities, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  Bound with Hearing
- Changes in Cost of Living, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Knitted Outerwear Industry, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No. 32 and the Administrator Vol. 3 [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 3)
  pg. 1-100
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No. 32 and the Administrator. Vol. 3 [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 4)
  pg. 100-209
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No. 32 and the Administrator. Vol 4 [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 5)
  Pages 1-314
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No. 32 and the Administrator Vol. 4 [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 6)
  Pages 315-448
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No.32 and the Administrator Vol. 5 [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No.32 and the Administrator Vol. 5 [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Changes in Cost of Living, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Current Status of Home Work in the Knitted Outerwear Industry, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Hearings Before the Knitted Outerwear Committee No.32 and the Administrator Vol. 6 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- CONOZCA Su Union (Box 71, Folder 9)
- CONOZCA Su Union (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Una Buena Union Nunca Descansa Local 105 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Title in Chinese (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Save our Benefits, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- What in the World is the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Doing? (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Salvemos Nuestros Beneficios Medicos, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Proteja Os Nossos Beneficios de Saude, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  Portuguese
- Save Our Health Benefits, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  Chinese
- What in the World is the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Doing? (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Como Entenderse Mejor (Box 71, Folder 9)
  Spanish; English
- Puede que Usted Califique para Recibir Dinero del Gobierno (Box 71, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Worker Family Education Program (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Talking Benefits, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Unite and Fight, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Cartoon in Chinese (Box 71, Folder 9)
  #1
- Cartoon in Chinese (Box 71, Folder 9)
  #2
- Save Our Health Benefits, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  Chinese; Copy #2
- Unite and Fight (Box 71, Folder 10)
  Chinese; Policy Statements Translated
- La Ley: Dice Que Usted Tiene el Derecho a Ingresar en Una Union (Box 71, Folder 10)
- United for Our Children (Box 71, Folder 10)
  English; Spanish; Chinese
- Consititucion: Sindicato Internacional de Trabajadores del Vestuario Femenino (Box 71, Folder 10)
- A Good Union Can Help You in Many Ways (Box 71, Folder 10)
  English; Spanish
- Pittston Guide Vol. 8- No. 1, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Pittston Guide Vol. 8- No. 1, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  Copy #2
- Reporter Trenton-Wilmington District Vol. 1- No. 9 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Reporter Trenton-Wilmington District Vol. 2- No. 10 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Reporter Trenton-Wilmington District Vol. 2- No. 12, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Upstate Organizer Vol. 1 No. 1, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Employees Benefit Plan, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- We Are the ILGWU (Box 71, Folder 10)
  Chinese; Photos: Robert Gumpert, Cara Lise Metz
- Nosotros Somos La ILGWU (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Title in Chinese (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Title in Chinese (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Employer Contributed Welfare Funds, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  Jan. 1 1962- Dec. 31 1964
- Una Historia Breve de la International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 71, Folder 11)
- A Brief History of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Employer Contributed Benefit Funds Report, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Financial Report Jan 1, 1989 to Dec. 31, 1991
- Proposed Amendments to the Constitution, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Recommended to the 40th Convention by the Constitution Revision Committee of the General Executive Board
- Freedom Award Dinner in Honor of David Dubinsky, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Article: "The Man Who Would Not Bargain" Patricia Daniels
- We Want a Real Union (Box 71, Folder 11)
  English; Spanish; authorization card
- We Want a Real Union (Box 71, Folder 11)
  English; Spanish; authorization card; Copy #2
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Jan-Feb. 1981
- Piece Rate Guide (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Northeast Department Dress Guide for Piece Rates, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Christine Dress; Local 233; Copy #1
- Northeast Department Dress Guide for Piece Rates, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  Christine Dress; local 233; Copy #2
- Piece Rate Guide, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  David Crystal
- Leslie-Fay, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- General Excellence Second Award Presented to Unite! Unite, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  Awarded in November 2003 for Outstanding Work During 2002 Calendar Year
- Original Credential Forty-First Convention (Box 71, Folder 12)
  Blank Certificate
- Duplicate Credential Forty-First Convention, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- One and One Half Years of Life and Activities 1916-1918 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  Report from the Joint Board of the New York Cloak, Skirt and Reefers Union
- Konvenshon Moskito, 1929 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Our First Fifty Years (Box 71, Folder 12)
  Knitgoods Workers Union Local 155
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- The ILGWU Song Book, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Convention Daily: Day One (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Let the Deliberations Begin!
- Convention Daily: Day 2 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Import Fight Must Continue
- Convention Daily: Day 3 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  "Proud of our Diversity"
- Convention Daily: Day 4 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Emma Mashinini; Shirley Carr
- Convention Daily: Day 5 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Brothers and Sisters, the Retirees of the ILGWU
- Convention Daily: Day 6 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  ILG Helps Put AT&T on Hold
- Convention: Day One, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  New York Welcomes ILG Delegates
- Convention Day 2, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  37th ILG Convention Opens
- Convention Day 3, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Carter: Side by Side With ILG
- Convention Day 4, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Spur Political Action vs. Rightist Threat
- Convention Day 6, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Organizing Today, High Fashion With a Label
- Convention Day 7, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  Re-elects Chaikin President
- On the Move, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Issue dedicated to "The Staff"
- On the Move Day One, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Getting There is Half the Fun?
- On the Move Day 2, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Innovations Built on Tradition
- On the Move Day 3, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- On the Move Day 4, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  An Injury to One is an Injury to All
- On the Move Day 5, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Delegates Tackle Tough Issues
- On the Move Day 6, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  We Can Stand & Deliver
- On the Move Final Day, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Three Top Officers Elected to Lead Union Through Next Three Years
- Unite and Fight Day Three, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Honoring Heroes of Our Time
- Unite and Fight Day Four, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Delegates Rally to Send AT&T a Wake- Up Call
- Moving Forward Together, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  ILGWU staffers roll, roll, roll the Convention on
- Moving Forward Together Day One, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  We Are Ready!
- Moving Forward Together Day Two, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Mazur Keynote
- Moving Forward Together Day Three, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  At the Mike
- Moving Forward Together Day Four, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Day of Decision
- Moving Forward Together Day Five, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Delegates Vote to Unite
- Moving Forward Together, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  Unite!
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 1, No. 3, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol.2, No. 1, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 2, No. 2, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 2, No. 2, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  The Case for Labor Law Reform
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 3, No. 1, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  What are Nontariff Barriers
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 6- No. 3 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  Urgent: A Stronger Minimum Wage
- Memo/ for Staff Only Vol. 7- No. 2, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  A Message from the President
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 8-No. 2, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  ILGWU General Council to be Formed
- Memo/for Staff Only Vol. 9- No. 2, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  How Mondale/Ferraro Can Win
- Publicity Guide (Box 71, Folder 16)
  Copy #1
- Publicity Guide (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Northeast Holiday Message (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Northeast Holiday Message (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Northeast Holiday Message (Box 71, Folder 17)
  Copy #3
- Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department Offensive Against Imports (Box 71, Folder 18)
- Report to the Delegates 38th Triennial Convention, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  Enclosed: ILGWU History and Coloring Books
- Employer Contributed Welfare Funds International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  1977-1979
- Brief History of the ILGWU (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Financial and Statistical Report International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Resolutions, 39th Convention International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Resolutions, 38th Convention, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Report of Proposed Amendments to the Constitution of the ILGWU, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- The Needle's Eye No. 71, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- The Needle's Eye No. 93, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  The Time is Now
- The Needle's Eye No. 95, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  Merry Christmas Everybody
- The Needle's Eye No. 100, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  On Oct. 9th 1968, Richard Nixon Said…
- The Needle's Eye No. 104, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  1974 Elections
- The Needle's Eye No. 111, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  1977 Elections
- The Needle's Eye No. 112, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- The Needle's Eye No. 114, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  Americans United for Labor Law Reform
- The Needle's Eye No. 118, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  Spoiling the Broth
- The Needle's Eye No. 122, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  High Stakes
- Delegate's Guide 37th Convention, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Convention: Day 1, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention
- Convention: Day 2, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Convention: Day 3, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; Carter: Side by Side With ILG
- Convention: Day 3, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; Carter: "Side by Side With ILG" Copy #2
- Convention: Day 4, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; Spur Political Action vs. Rightist Threat
- Convention: Day 4, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; Spur Political Action vs. Rightist Threat; Copy #2
- Convention: Day 5, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; All Committees Reporting
- Convention: Day 5, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; All Committees Reporting; Copy #2
- Convention: Day 6, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  37th Convention; Organizing Today
- Convention Daily: Day 4, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  39th Convention; Emma Mashinini and Shirley Carr
- Convention Daily: Day 5, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  39th Convention; "Brothers and Sisters, the Retirees of the ILGWU"
- Convention Daily: Day 6, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  39th Convention; ILG Helps Put AT&T on Hold
- Report of Proposed Amendments to the Constitution of the ILGWU, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  39th Convention
- Convention Daily: Day 2, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  37th Convention; Import Fight Must Continue
- Convention Daily: Day 3, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  39th Convention; "Proud of Our Diversity"
- Convention Daily: Day 4, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Delegate's Guide to 38th ILGWU Convention, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Convention: Day 1, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; Welcome to the 38th Convention
- Convention: Day 2, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; Chaikin Opens 38th Convention
- Convention: Day 3, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; Goals for America
- Convention: Day 4, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; 801 ILGWU Delegates
- Convention: Day 5, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention
- Convention: Day 6, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; Hail Mondale: "The Road Ahead"
- Convention: Day 7, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  38th Convention; Chaikin Wins Third Term as President
- Union Worker, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  November
- Union Worker, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  November; Copy #2
- Union Worker, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  November; Copy #3
- Union Worker, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  June
- Union Worker, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  March
- Union Worker, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  October-November
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  David Gingold
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  David Gingold; Jan-Feb; Copy #2
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  David Gingold; Jan.-Feb.; Copy #3
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  September
- Union Worker, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Union Worker Vol. 1- No. 1, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  October
- Union Worker Vol.1- NO.1, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  October; Copy #2
- A Time for Recognition, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  Program for Honoring the Retirement of George Pishko
- Northeast Department 30th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  1935-1965
- Silver Jubilee, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  Accomplishment Overview
- Coats & Suits & You (Box 71, Folder 29)
  Style Guide on Coats
- Respect: The Thread that Binds Us, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  Burning Desire… No More Plant Closings
- Respect: The Thread that Binds Us, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  Burning Desire… No More Plant Closings; Copy #2
- A Brief History of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (Box 71, Folder 31)
- Your Union (Box 71, Folder 31)
  A Handbook of Information for ILGWU Members
- Your Union (Box 71, Folder 31)
  A Handbook of information for ILGWU Members; Copy #2
- Needle News Vol. 19, No. 2, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 32)
- Serving Circle, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 33)
- Serving Circle, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 33)
- Welcome to Your Union Health Center (Box 71, Folder 34)
- Welcome to Your Union Health Center (Box 71, Folder 34)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Region Anniversary Issue, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 35)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  1st Anniversary
- 1980 ILGWU Calendar Portraits of People (Box 71, Folder 37)
- Death Benefit Fund, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  Article 13 from the Constitution of the ILGWU
- ILGWU Staff Retirement Fund, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  Summary and Plan
- Official Withdrawal Certificate (Box 71, Folder 38)
- Stress: A Fact of Life? (Box 71, Folder 38)
  How to deal with stress in the workplace; Copy #2
- Stress: a Fact of Life? (Box 71, Folder 38)
  How to deal with stress in the workplace
- Stress: A Fact of Life? (Box 71, Folder 38)
  How to deal with stress in the workplace; Copy#3
- Sanitation in Garment Shops (Box 71, Folder 38)
  How to Keep the Workplace Clean
- Sanitation in Garment Shops (Box 71, Folder 38)
  How to Keep the Workplace Clean; Copy #2
- Solvent Use in Apparel Manufacturing (Box 71, Folder 38)
- Solvent Use in Apparel Manufacturing (Box 71, Folder 38)
- The ILGWU Health & Safety Department (Box 71, Folder 38)
- The ILGWU Health & Safety Department (Box 71, Folder 38)
- The ILGWU Health & Safety Department (Box 71, Folder 38)
- Jimmy Carter and Walter Mondale Fought to Protect Our Jobs. Now They Need Our Help! (Box 71, Folder 39)
- Jimmy Carter and Walter Mondale Fought to Protect Our Jobs. Now They Need Our Help! (Box 71, Folder 39)
- Jimmy Carter and Walter Mondale Fought to Protect Our Jobs. Now They Need Our Help! (Box 71, Folder 39)
- The Torch Vol. X, No. I, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 40)
- 1984 Calendar (Box 71, Folder 40)
  English; Chinese; Spanish
- Pins and Needles: Musical Revue of the '30s (Box 71, Folder 41)
- Desert Storm Musical Extravaganza, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  Program
- Desert Storm Musical Extravaganza, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  Program; Copy #2
- Up 'n At 'Em, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- Up n' At 'Em, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- ILG Raves of 1966 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- ILG Raves of '69, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- ILG Raves of '69, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- ILG Raves of '69, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  Program; Copy #3
- The Lady and the Gangsters, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- The Lady and the Gangsters, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 41)
- Scranton District Bulletin, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 42)
- Scranton District Bulletin, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 42)
- The ILG'er, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 42)
- Social Cost Analysis of Layoffs of Leslie Fay Workers in Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 43)
- Social Cost Analysis of Layoffs of Leslie Fay Workers in Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 43)
- "Tee-Off"- A Musical Comedy, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 44)
- A Policy Guide on Enforcing the Union Agreement, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 45)
- Pittston Guide, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.2: no.1 (1973:June)
- Pittston Guide, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.2: no.1 (1973: June); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.3: no.1 (1974: Dec)
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.5: no.2 (1978: June)
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.6: no.2 (1979:Oct)
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.6: n.2 (1979: Oct); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.6: no.2 (1979, Oct); Copy #3
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.5: no.3 (1978: Nov)
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.5: no.3 (1978: Nov); Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.5: no.3 (1978: Nov); Copy #3
- Pittston Guide, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  v.6: no.1 (1979; Mar)
- Pittston Guide, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.7: no.2 (1980: Oct)
- Pittston Guide, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.7: no.2 (1980, Oct); Copy #2
- Pittston, PA, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.7: no.2 (1980: Oct); copy#3
- Pittston Guide, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.8: no.1 (1981: Jan-Feb)
- Pittston Guide, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.8: no.2 (1981: Nov)
- Pittston Guide, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 47)
- Pittston Guide, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.8: no.2 (1981: Nov.) Copy #2
- Pittston Guide, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  v.9: no.2 (1982: Fall)